<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mastermind Game</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="instruction">The idea of the game is for one player (the code-breaker) to guess the secret code chosen by the other player (the code-maker). The code is a sequence of 4 colored pegs chosen from eight colors available. The code-breaker makes a series of pattern guesses - after each guess the code-maker gives feedback in the form of 2 numbers, the number of pegs that are of the right color and in the correct position, and the number of pegs that are of the correct color but not in the correct position - these numbers are usually represented by small black and white pegs.\n\nThe board is the divided into three (3) parts arranged vertically, which represented by figure 1 --- 1] the code maker hidden pegs, 2] the code breaker game board, and 3] the code breaker peg option part.
\nThe code maker hidden pegs is where the hidden pegs are located. At the end of the game the colored peg combination made by the code maker will be displayed in this area. The result of the game will also be displayed in this area through the text located below the hidden pegs. (Figure #1)
\nThe code breaker game board is where the player --- that is the code breaker --- positioned his guesses, see figure #2. This part is divided into three (3) columns: the black, guess pegs, and white column. These columns are further divided into eight (8) rows which corresponds to the number of attempts a code breaker to reveal the hidden colored pegs made by the code maker. The numbers on the black column represents the total number of guessed pegs which are of the right color and in the correct position while the number inside the white box in the white column indicates the total number of colored pegs which correctly corresponds to the color from the hidden pegs by the code maker but are in the wrong position. The guess of the code breaker will be displayed in the guess pegs.
\nThis part of the board is divided into two (2) areas: the colored peg options, and the action-button options, see figure #3. The colored peg options consist of eight (8) colored pegs where the code breaker can choose from by clicking the desired peg to make his guess. The code breaker is only allowed to make a combination of four (4) pegs that will correspond to the total number of hidden pegs. The action-button options on the other hand consist of two (2) different buttons: the CHECK, and ERASE buttons. The CHECK button once clicked will submit the created guess by the code breaker and an evaluation of the submitted guess will be displayed accordingly, and that is to the black and white column. Also once the guess is submitted the number of attempts in guessing will be deducted by one. The ERASE button allows player to delete peg from his created guess. The deletion of peg will be one peg per click that will start from right to left or from the latest to oldest peg.
</string>
</resources>
